A Guide to the Additional Papers of Douglas H. Gordon, 1934-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- European Travel 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 3)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Martin Breslauer, Craddock & Barnard, Frederick B. Daniell & Son, Leggatt Brothers, H. Blairman & Sons, Mallet at Bourdon House Limited, London; Paris dealers--Cailliux, Marc Loliee, Georges Heilbrun, Pierre Beres; J[ames] Rives Childs, Randolph-Macon College, Ashland; Jean-Francoise Ceresole, Geneva, Switzerland; Sir Robert Abdy (1896- ) and Lady Jane Abdy, Ferrers, Piccadilly Arcade, London; George J[oseph] Levy (1927- ), London; Jacques Guignard, Bibliotheque de L'Arsenal, Paris; Herman Liebaers, Kononklicke Bibliotheek van Belgie, Brussels, Belgium; Edward H[owell] Sims (1923- ), American Consul, Consulate General of the United States of America, Munich, Germany; John [Waynflete] Carter, Sotheby of London, New York; Auguste Lambiotte, Brussels, Belgium; Barbara D. Sizer re routine legal matters; medical reports for Douglas Huntly Gordon; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Holland; Diana Mary Reynolds Brewis, Surrey, England; international driving permit for Gordon; international certificates of vaccination for Gordon]
- European Travel 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 3)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Charles J. Sawyer Booksellers, David Peel & Company Ltd., Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Craddock & Barnard, Frederick B. Daniell & Son, H. D. Lyon Antiquarian Bookseller; Paris dealers--Lecomte-Ullmann, Cailleux, Etienne Rossignol, Marc Loliee; Sir David Piper (1918-1990), National Portrait Gallery, London; D[avid] M[cBeth] Sutherland, Taylor Institution, University of Oxford; list of monies owed to European dealers; Hannah J[ohnson] Howell (1905-1988), Frick Art Reference Library, New York; Elizabeth Clare, New York; Edward Ligon Castleton, Baltimore; Blackwell's, Oxford; Peter Bell, The Hall, Thirsk, Yorkshire; C. Hugh Hildesley, Park-Bernet Galleries, Inc., New York; Lucien Scheler, Librairie Thomas-Scheler, Paris; Jean Francoise Ceresole, Geneva, Switzerland; M. Knoedler & Company Inc., New York; Mildred Steinbach (1906- ), Frick Art Reference Library, New York; Laurence Ewald; N[ikolaus (Bernhard Leon)] Pevsner (1902-1983), Birkbeck College, University of London; Frederic A[ndrews] Gibbs (1903-1992), Chicago, Illinois; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire; Barbara D. Sizer re routine legal matters; Robert [Lewis Wright] Collison (1914-1989), The British Broadcasting Corporation, London; Claude Tchou, Paris]
- European Travel 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  [London dealers--H. W. Keil Ltd., Lucien Goldschmidt, P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Craddock & Barnard; Paris dealers--Lecomte-Ullmann, Marc Loliee, Georges Heilbrun; A[lfred] L[eslie] Rowse (1903-), All Souls College, Oxford; Bodleian Library, Oxford; Robert [Andre Edouard] Baldick (1927-1972), Pembroke College, Oxford; Gino Cenedese, Murano, Venice, Italy; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire; Sir Robert Abdy and Lady Jane Abdy, Ferrers, Piccadilly Arcade, London; Yvon [Charles] Bizardel (1891- ), Paris; Leslie Cheek, Jr. (1908-1992), Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Richmond; Jacques Guignard, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; J[ames] Rives Childs, Randolph-Macon College, Ashland]
- European Travel 1968-1969, 2 folders (Box 3)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., H. W. Keil Ltd., Gander & White Ltd., Martin Breslauer, Bernard Quaritch Ltd., David Peel & Company Ltd., Frederic B. Daniell & Son; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Georges Heilbru; Christina Behm Nunes re routine legal matters; International Bar Association 1968 Conference; Jacques Guignard, Bibliotheque de L'Arsenal, Paris; [Thomas] Humphrey Brooke (1914-1988), London; R[ichard] A[nthony] Sayce, Worchester College, Oxford; William P[atrick] Fay (1909-1969), Ambassador of Ireland, Embassy of Ireland, Washington, D. C.; Lady Rosalie [Glynn Grylls] Mander (1905- ), Wightwick Manor, Wolverhampton, England; Sir Gyles Isham (1903-1976), Lamport Hall, Northampton, England; Diane Mary Reynolds Brewis, Surrey, England; Ian Lowe (1935- ), Ashmolean Museum, Oxford; Robert [Andre Edouard] Baldick, Pembroke College, Oxford; Boyd Alexander (1913-1980), Prospect House, Upton, Didcot, Berks, England; Lady Jane Abdy, London; Sidney C[harles] Hutchison (1912- ), Royal Academy of Arts, Piccadilly, London; brochures on Dublin, Ireland; Lucien Scheler, Librairie Thomas-Scheler, Paris; A[lfred] L[eslie] Rowse (1903- ), San Marino, California; Gino Cenedese, Murano, Venice, Italy; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire; C. Kingsley Adams, London; Robert Shackleton (1919-1986), Bodleian Library, Oxford; Desmond [Walter] Guinness (1931- ), Leixlip Castle, County Kildaire, Eire]
- European Travel 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 3)
  [London dealers--Martin Breslauer, P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., H. Blairman & Sons, J. H. Bourdon-Smith Ltd. Antique Silver; Bernard Quaritch Ltd.,; Paris dealers--Georges Heilbrun, Etienne Rossignol, Marc Loliee; Lady Rosalie [Glynn Grylls] Mander, Wightwick Manor, Wolverhampton, England; Jean Barbey, Paris; Christina Behm Nunes re routine legal matters; pamphlet, Corneille; list of passengers for the R.M.S. Queen Elizabeth II; [Thomas] Humphrey Brooke (1914- 1988), Lime Kiln, Claydon, Suffolk, England; Sir Roy [Colin] Strong (1935- ), National Portrait Gallery, London; C. Kingsley Adams, London; Boyd Alexander, Prospect House, Upton, Didcot, Berks, England; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire, England; Jacques Guignard, Bibliotheque de L'Arsenal, Paris; Yvon [Charles] Bizardel, Paris; George J[oseph] Levy, London; Philip Kolb (1907-1992), University of Illinois, Urbana; typescripts re St. Francis of Assisi]
- European Travel 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd., P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Maggs Brothers Ltd., H. Blairman & Sons; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Etienne Rossignol; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois, Urbana; Denys [Miller] Sutton (1917-1991), Apollo, London; J[ohn] William Middendorf (1924- ), Embassy of the United States of America, The Hague, Holland; Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; Sir Esmond [Otho] Durlacher (1901-1982), Grosvenor Square, London; William Nichols, The American Library in Paris; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Holland; letter from Barbados Hill, Devon, Pennsyvania re "Roddy" [Rodney Gerald] Searight (1909- ); George J[oseph] Levy; C. Kinsgley Adams, London; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire, England]
- European Travel 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd.,Winifred A. Meyers (Autographs) Ltd., John Baskett Ltd., David Peel & Company Ltd.; Paris dealers--Etienne Rossignol, Marc Loliee; Lucien Scheler, Librairie Thomas-Scheler, Paris; Lorenzo Rubelli & Figlio, Venezia, Italy; Georges Dethan (1923- ), Paris; Harvey White, Reading, Berkshire, England; John Baskett (1930- ), London; Boyd Alexander, Prospect House, Upton, Didcot, Berkshire, England; Julien Cain, Musee Jacquemart-Andre, Paris; Cyril Humphris, London; Davies & Son, London; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire, England; Roger Devauchelle, Paris; B[ ] Montgolfier, Bellevue, France; Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Holland; C. Kingsley Adams, London; Henry Ringling North (1909-1993), Rome, Italy; offprint, Studies on Voltaire and the Eighteenth Century by Colin Duckworth; Greek memorabilia; brochures and printed on Swans Hellenic Cruises including ship passes]
- European Travel 1972-1973, 3 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--Bernard Quaritch Ltd., John Baskett Ltd., P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Craddock & Barnard, Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd., Marlborough Rare Books Ltd.; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Etienne Rossignol, Galignani; Nicholas J. Barker, The Book Collector, London; Robin Hutchison, Scottish National Portrait Gallery, Edinburgh; John Kerslake, National Portrait Gallery, London; R[ichard] A[nthony] Sayce, Worchester College, London; Kate Rau, Ripon, Yorkshire, England re death of Arthur Rau; Gino Cenedese, Murano, Venice, Italy; Sir Gyles Isham, The Old Rectory, Lamport, Northampton, England; A[lfred] L[eslie] Rowse, All Souls College, Oxford; Jacques Poyer (1936- ), Secretaire General du Guard, Nimes, France; Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; Ian Lowe, Department of Western Art, Ashmolean Museum, Oxford; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois, Urbana; Jan A. J. M.van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; Arthur Rau, Yorkshire, England; Lady Rosalie [Glynn Grylls] Mander, Wightwick Manor, Wolverhampton, England; Alice Dodge, English Watercolors and Drawings, London; Roger Devauchelle, Paris with brochure on his exhibition; program, Creations a la Comedie Francaise; Lorenzo Rubelli and Figlio, Venezia, Italy; Douglas G[ordon] Carroll (1915- ), Baltimore, Maryland]
- European Travel 1957-1976, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd.; Paris dealers--Librairie Lardanchet; Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; dividends statements; John W[illiam] Jolliffe (1929- ), Bodleian Library, Oxford; Orest A[llen] Ranum (1933- ), Aveyron, France; Charles L[ouis] Marburg (1906- ), The English-Speaking Union, New York; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; Colin [Ellis] Franklin (1923- ), Culham, Oxford; Musee National du Chateau de Blerancourt]
- European Travel 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--Bernard Quaritch Ltd., P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Martin Breslauer, Craddock & Barnard; Paris dealers--Georges Heilbrun, Marc Loliee, Etienne Rossignol; Nicolas J[ohn] Barker (1932- ), The Book Collector, London; death of Julien Cain; Harvey and Diana White, London; W[illiam] H[enry] Bond (1915- ), The Houghton Library, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts; Yvon [Charles] Bizardel, Marne, France; William Salloch (1906- ), Rare Books, Ossining, New York; Christina Thoresby, Venice, Italy; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Ian Lowe, Ashmolean Museum, Oxford; William Porter, School of Music, Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois; R[ichard] A[nthony] Sayce, Worcester College, Oxford; Geoffrey Cradock-Watson, Gloucestershire, England; Kate Rau, Yorkshire, England; Lilian [Maria Charlotte] Randall (1931- ), The Walters Art Gallery, Baltimore, Maryland; Jacques Guignard, Bibliotheque de L'Arsenal, Paris; Lawrence Weston Krieger, New York re marriage of Carlo Von Roth and Maria Koschir; Jan A. J. M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; M[ichael] A[ndrew] Screech (1926- ), Department of French and Language and Literature, University College, London; Giles [Gaudard] Barber (1930- ), Oxford University, brochures re France; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Aveyron, France]
- European Travel 1974-1976, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Hatchards Booksellers, Bernard Quaritch Ltd.; Paris dealers--Librairie Lardanchet, Marc Loliee, Georges Heilbrun, Pasque; pamphlet, Valentin Kraer, Gibbon's Bookbinder at Lausanne, by B. H. Breslauer; Christina Thoresby, Venice, Italy; Harvey White, London; Yvon [Charles] Bizardel, Nogent sur Marne, France; Robert L[eRoy] Bartley (1937- ), The Wall Street Journal, New York; Lucien Scheler, Librairie Thomas-Scheler, Paris; John Kerslake, National Portrait Gallery, London; C[olin] R[yder] Duckworth (1926- ), University of Auckland, Auckland, New Zealand; memorial for Charles Kingsley Adams; Cecil B[urton] Lyon (1903-1993), IRC, New York; M[ichael] A[ndrew] Screech, University College, London; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Richard A[nthony] Sayce, Cornwall, England; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Aveyron, France; Gyles Isham, Lamport Hall, Northampton, England]
- European Travel 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Sotheby Parke Bernet and Company; Paris dealers--Georges Heilbrun, Etienne Rossignol, Marc Loliee; Edwin Engelberts, Geneva, Switzerland; Florimond Tulkens, Brussels, Belgium; Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; Ian Lowe, The Ashmolean Museum, Oxford; Peter Cooper in Stockholm, Sweden; Richard A[nthony] Sayce, Worcester College, Oxford; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Aveyron, France; Laurence Ewald; Carlos van Hasselt, Fondation Custodia, Paris; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; John [Ralph Sidney] Guinness (1935- ), Hereford Square, London; M[ichael] A[ndrew] Screech, University College, London; Harvey White, London; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; Lady Rosalie [Glynn Grylls] Mander, London; reprint, The Dutch East-Indiamen: Their Sailors, Their Navigators and Life on Board 1602-1795, by C. R. Boxer; pamphlet, The History of a Great Collection re the works of August Edouart]
- European Travel 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 4)
  [London dealers--P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd.; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Georges Heilbrun; Walter Nagel, New York; Digby [Reymond] Collett-Franklin (1908- ), Kent, England; Charles [Montgomery] Monteith (1921- ), Faber and Faber Ltd. Publishers, London; John Beverley Riggs, Eleutherian Mills Historical Library, Greenville, Wilmington, Delaware; Jean Adhemar (1908-1987), Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Stewart [Henry] Perowne (1901-1989), London; Harvey White, Osler Club of London; Laurence Ewald; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Aveyron, France; Annie [Anne Elizabeth] Shaver-Crandell (1941- ), Florence, Italy; Peter Cooper, Sussex, England; Christina Thoresby, Venice, Italy; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; Maurice Zuber, Guillon, France; E[dward] D[ouglas] Guinness, Venice, Italy; Jean-Baptiste Giard, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Boyd Alexander, Prospect House, Upton, Didcot, Oxford]
- European Travel 1977-1979 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Hatchards Booksellers, Christie's, Somerville & Simpson Ltd., Maggs Brothers Ltd., Thomas Agnew & Sons Ltd., Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd.; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Librairie Galignani; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Laurence Ewald; Harvey White, London; Evelyn Joll, London; Grace Cahlander and Janet Lamberti, Charlecote House re household business; Jan A.J.M. van Zuylen, Dordrecht, Netherlands; Yvon [Charles] Bizardel, Nogent sur Marne, France; Maurice Zuber, Guillon, France; M[ichael] A[ndrew] Screech, University College, London; Alliance Francaise de Washington, Washington, D.C.; Nicholas [John] Barker, The Book Collector, London; Stewart [Henry] Perowne, London; Boyd Alexander, Prospect House, Upton, Didcot, Oxford
- European Travel 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Bernard Quaritch Ltd., P. & D. Colnaghi and Company Ltd., Christie's, Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd., Somerville & Simpson Ltd.; Paris dealers--Marc Loliee, Librairie Lardanchet; Jean-Baptiste Giard, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Roger Devauchelle, Paris; Franco Matania (1922- ), The Alpine Gallery, London; Ian Lowe, The Ashmolean Museum, Oxford; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Thomas Ward, Baltimore, Maryland re proposed variance for Loyola College; J[ames] Rives Childs, The Jefferson, Richmond, Virginia; Harvey White, London; Wesley Wilson, Walters Art Gallery, Baltimore Museum; Peter and Gwyneth Cooper, Sussex, England; Nicolas J[ohn] Barker, The Book Collector, London; Maurice and Mary Catherine Zuber, Guillon, France; Gerard Mourgue (1921- ), Radio France, Paris]
- European Travel 1978-1980 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--J.H. Bourdon-Smith Ltd. Antique Silver, Christie's, Hatchards Booksellers, Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd.; Paris dealers--Librairie Lardanchet; dividends statement; John Kerslake, National Portrait Gallery, London; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Aveyron, France; Diana Mary Reynolds Brewis, Isle of Man, Great Britain; Carlos van Hasselt, Fondation Custodia, Paris; Harvey White, London; Anne [Dahlgren] Hecht (1926- ), New York; A[lfred] L[eslie] Rowse, Cornwall, England; Jacques Guignard; Gerard Mourgue, Radio France, Paris; Sir Valentine [Robert Duff] Abdy (1937- ), "Newton-Ferrers," Callington, Cornwall, England; Sidney C[harles] Hutchison, Royal Academy of Arts, Piccadilly, London; Georges Le Rider, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Anne (Adams) Duckworth, Leicestershire, England; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Kenneth [John] Garlick (1916- ), The Ashmolean Museum, Oxford]
- European Travel 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Hatchards Booksellers, Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Christie's, J.H. Bourdon-Smith Ltd.; Paris dealers--Librairie Lardanchet, Librairie Galignani, Librairie Marc Loliee; Roger Pierrot, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Peter and Gwyneth Cooper, Sussex, England; Harvey White, London; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Maurice and Mary Catherine Zuber, Guillon, France; Philippe Aries (1914-1984), Maisons-Laffitte, France; Leslie [Alan] Dunkling (1935- ), Thames Ditton, Surrey, England; Monique Lambert, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Robert L. Nikirk (d. 1990), The Grolier Club, New York; Gerard Mourgue, Courbevoie, France; John Kerslake, National Portrait Gallery, London; printed, Guide a l'usage des Amateurs de Livres/Repertoire des Members du Syndicat National de la Librairie Ancienne et Moderne; Nicolas [John] Barker, The British Library, London]
- European Travel 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Winifred A. Myers (Autographs) Ltd., Somerville & Simpson Ltd., Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Hatchards Booksellers, Christie's; Paris dealers--Librairie Marc Loliee, Librairie Galignani, Librairie Lardanchet; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Christopher [Martin Bevan] (1923- ), London; Roger Pierrot, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; Robert Driant, Vernouillet, France re General Boulander; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Nancy E. Paige, Baltimore, Maryland re settlement with Loyola College; Jean-Baptiste Giard, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; medical reports for Douglas Huntly Gordon; Orest [Allen] Ranum, Paris; Maurice and Mary Catherine Zuber, Guillon, France; Harvey White, London; Philippe Aries, Maisons-Laffitte, France]
- European Travel 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Craddock & Barnard, Hatchards Booksellers, Christie's; Griselda Hamilton-Baillie, Royal Academy Trust, Royal Academy of Arts, Piccadilly, London; medical reports for Douglas Huntly Gordon; Robert G[raff] Merrick, Baltimore, Maryland; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; "Peculiarities of Charlecote House"; Maurice and Mary Catherine Zuber, Paris; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; Harvey White, London; Franco Matania, London--invitation to art exhibition; Portugese National Tourist Office, New York; Roger Pierrot, Bibliotheque Nationale, Paris; [Thomas] Humphrey Brooke, London; John W[illiam] Jolliffe, Bodleian Library, Oxford University, Oxford; Bodley's American Friends Newsletter and brochure]
- European Travel 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Christie's, Hatchards Booksellers, Bernard Quaritch Ltd., Thomas Agnew & Sons Ltd.--including catalog of "111th Annual Exhibition of Watercolours and Drawings"; Nicolas J[ohn] Barker, The British Library, London; James W[illard] B[artlett] Benkard (1937- ), New York; American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust, New York; Christopher M[artin] Bevan, Gray's Inn, London; Christina Thoresby, Venice, Italy; Griselda Hamilton-Baillie, Royal Academy Trust, Royal Academy of Arts, Piccadilly, London; J[ohn] W[illiam] Jolliffe, Bodleian Library, Oxford; Douglas H. Gordon Ex Libris(bookplates); exhibition notes for "T. J. Cobden-Sanderson Bookbindings 1884-1893", The British Library]
- European Travel 1985 (Box 5)
  [London dealers--Somerville & Simpson Ltd., Hatchards Booksellers, Christie's; Paris dealers-- Librairie Lardanchet; Kathrine [Margaret] Ockenden (1932- ), American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust, New York; Robert B[rown] M[orrison] Barton (1903-1995), Corn Bay Associates, Beverly, Massachusetts; Grace Cahlander, Charlecote House re household business; Orest A[llen] Ranum, Aveyron, France; medical reports for Douglas Huntly Gordon; R[ichard] J[ulian] Roberts (1930- ), Bodleian Library, Oxford; Philip Kolb, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign; American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust, New York; Sandra Hindman [Hoadley] (1944- ), Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois; Sir Michael [Vincent] Levey (1927- ), National Gallery, London; Maurice and Mary Catherine Zuber, Paris]
- European Travel 1987 (Box 5)
- European Travel 1988 (Box 5)
- Photographs of Douglas Huntly Gordon and Winifred Macmillan Claude Gordon at Charlecote House, in the library and in the gardens, and on the S.S United Statesca. 1934-1980 (Box 5)
- Catalogue of the Early French Books of the Charlecote House Library, Volumes I and II n.d., Bound volume
- Catalogue of the Later French Books of the Charlecote House Library n.d., Bound volume